As we all travel across
the sea Raising our
voices we take In the beautiful blue world
Our spirits ready to go Everybody rejoices
Now let's go Get the sails all unfurled
yeah yeah Here we are
in between the sea and
the sky Ready now for adventure We're itching
to try Get ready to roam So all aboard
now we're set to go Set sail to the ocean
so deep Ready for a truly grand adventure
Well don't you think that sounds really
fun All this excitement is second to none
As we all travel across
the sea Raising our
voices we take In the beautiful blue world
Our spirits ready to go Everybody rejoices
Now let's go get the sales all unfurled
If there's something that I just won't ever
forget It's the way that I felt when our
journey was set Now I won't be scared as
long as I keep that
feeling there With that,
let us keep up the pace While
enjoying every trip from place to
place Our timid hearts get the
rhythm ingrained So let's keep going,
adventure awaits So many treasures
await So now let's raise our voices
in pride Laughing out when they are
found With all the riches in hand,
everybody rejoices Party on,
cause we stand tall and proud
Life is adventurous, be aware it's
dangerous Who's gonna be one of us?
And a trip goes on because.
We're the pirates of the mass.
To the west, to the east.
Gotta find my way, sail away,
all the way to one piece.
Bring all your dreams with
you, now fill the void.
In your heart, spread your wings.
And believe that you can soar.
Just let the breeze guide the way.
Till you're ready to start up once again.
Now you're ready for more.
So many treasures away.
So now let's raise our voices in pride.
Laughing out when they are found.
With all the riches in hand.
Everybody rejoices, party on.
Cause we stand tall and proud!
Don't know those two, but whatever.
So let's see here.
There's that Straw Hat
guy, orange hair lady,
and awesome superhero.
That's five down and three to go.
Wonder where they're hiding.
Hey, she's up.
Are you all right, mistress?
I can't take it anymore!
Mistress Corona!
Calm down, milady.
It's just us, your loyal servants.
Let's go away!
We brought you to safety,
but you've been crying about roaches
in your sleep for a while now.
Where are we?
We didn't see any signs of the enemy.
We just found you laying
down, foaming at the mouth.
Who in the world could
have done that to you?
Was it that nose guy from before?
Why is the mansion falling apart?
What's that rumbling?
Don't tell me those pirates
are on a rampage again.
The pirates are still going
on a rampage, I think.
But it's actually Ors that's
causing all this destruction.
You're kidding me.
I hate to say this, but from what we
heard, Ors didn't just wreck the mansion.
He crushed the zombie generals, too.
But they're the strongest
zombies we've got.
So it turns out Moria can't
control Ors after all?
Well, he is really big.
Oh, no, you guys! You got my bro!
I heard a girl!
What?
What does he want?
This might be a good time to tell
you that he kind of stumped on Dr.
Hogback, too.
He did what?
I was wrong.
Hey, lady!
I can't take this!
If he's looking for a girl, who
knows what he'll do if he finds me?
Between him and the pirates,
this place is doomed!
I'm out of here!
I need you guys to grab all the
treasure and all the food you can carry!
I'm gonna steal their pirate ship and run!
What pirate ship?
The Straw Hats!
Now, before we all get crushed, let's go!
As you wish, mistress!
What? Whoa! No! Stop it! What are you
doing? Where am I? Cut it out! Damn it!
So she finally woke up, huh?
Well, that won't stop me!
Come on, my dear!
I already went through
all the boring stuff!
Just let me kiss you, something
to me, husband and wife!
I said no!
No!
Those aren't even human licks and I'm a
pirate, I'm into adventure, not romance!
But I'm the Graveyard King!
You'll be the Graveyard Queen!
Doesn't that sound wonderful?
What does that even mean?
Lola, no!
Namizo, you.
How dare you do this to me, you traitor?
You said Master Ab and I
would make a beautiful couple.
Then I turn around for five
minutes and you're marrying him?
You said you were my friend,
but all you wanted was my man.
I should have known better
than to trust a thief like you.
Hold on a second, Lili.
You've got this all wrong.
I mean, for one, I was
knocked out this entire time.
I don't have a clue what...
Is this a wedding dress?
Why am I wearing this?
It's pretty, though.
It's pretty, huh?
How wonderful for you!
This is all a big misunderstanding!
That is enough!
Why don't you just bury
your rotting carcass in
a hole somewhere so I
can get married already?
If you want to get married, marry me!
I would rather die!
My poor little ab ignorant
to the terrifying truth.
This so-called woman's real name
is Namizo, and she's really...
a man!
No!
That can't be true!
Oh, that's right.
I almost forgot I told her that.
But wait.
I saw her in the back. I know I did.
Get the hell out of
here, you filthy traitor!
I'm telling you, it's not my fault!
No kidding, I'm right, Lola!
She keeps missing me.
A Miss.
What?
Run for it while you still can.
I'll hold him off, but I don't
know how long I can last.
I came here to save you, my friend.
Lola.
Come here, mess your arm.
That's right, sweetheart.
If you're looking for a kiss,
then pucker up because Lola's got
a big wet one right here for you.
Lola.
Damn it!
My bride's getting away!
Your bride's right here, baby!
Nice try, but you can't convince
me that my bride's a man.
Now move or suffer!
Papa!
You're nothing but a lowly zombie.
How dare you make me waste so
much strength disposing of you!
That's a good girl.
Finally West up and
stopped running, did you?
You can't hide!
And you can't escape!
Because wherever you may
go, I'll hunt you down!
And I can assure you,
you'll never see me coming.
Now, Thunder Charge!
How dare you.
I came here to save you, my friend.
You can't do that to Lola.
Yes, my dear.
Come flying into your husband's arms.
Swing!
I know this isn't enough to beat you,
but I'll be damned if I don't try.
Huh?
Hmm.
I don't get it.
It hardly seemed to hurt him at
all the last time I did that.
It's only natural, I suppose.
Close.
That pervert he was fighting
earlier really wore him out.
He was already well past his limit.
Well, whatever, right?
I win! Yeah!
I guess I must have hit
his weak spot or something.
Lola!
Are you okay? Hang in there.
Thank you.
I don't know what I would have
done if you hadn't shown up.
You don't have to thank me, Namizo.
we're friends right i owe you an apology
lola when i first saw you i was scared and
i told you a lie it's just that i thought
if i said it was a man
you'd leave me alone
you're big silly it was
pretty obvious i guess so
wait just a second absalom is completely
helpless right now i'm
gonna make you mine baby
anybody in there Straw Hat
baby orange hair lady hero
guy what was his name again
oh uh i think it was roast
right no not even close i
think it had an s at the end
didn't it shoes yeah I think
you're getting colder actually
fours no wait that's close
but it's oars that's it oh
I'm sorry but my injuries
are quite terrible it's fine
we understand you can still
move around though right
yeah then move yourself out
of the way of course hey oars
If that's really Luffy's
shadow you've got inside you,
then I probably shouldn't
have to tell you this.
But you should never underestimate
the strength of your own crew.
You tiny pirates are tougher
than I thought you'd be.
I'm tired of being thrown around so much.
What do you say we turn the tables
and throw him around for a change?
Huh?
Hey, come on, Zoro!
I can get behind that. Huh?
We've let him have his
fun for long enough.
Hey, whoa, wait a minute!
How are we supposed to throw him?
In case you haven't noticed, he's a giant!
We noticed.
And don't forget, he's got Luffy's
speed and fighting skills as well.
You know, I think he would
make a terrible Pirate King.
So how do we want to approach this, then?
I got a ton of plans.
One of them's got to work.
He has to have some kind of a wait point.
When you're frying a fish this big,
you gotta scale and de-bone it
before you put it in the pan.
Maybe it's not completely
hopeless, but I'm scared.
Smash it down!
Here he comes.
No, no, no!
Giant foot score!
That is not one of Loopy's moves!
No!
Stop it!
Franky, look out!
He's coming right for you!
Hammer!
Okay, punk, you've only left
us with one option here.
You want to fight?
Then feel the power of all of us combined!
Heads up, you guys!
I know the plan!
We're taking him down with Tactic 15!
We're what?
Really?
But it's still untested!
Zoro! Eyebrows! Stand by!
Just grab one of our legs!
This feels like it's about to get weird.
Here we go!
Let's do this!
Hey, I'm stuck in six!
Giant robot warrior!
Emperor!
Hey, wait a minute, Franky!
We're not complete!
The left arm still isn't docked yet!
What the hell are you doing to us, Robin?
Hurry up and duck onto my left arm!
Robin, we need you!
Come on, it's fine!
Just do what I'm doing!
I'm not embarrassing myself like that.
What's the matter?
She won't do it? What?
Why are you acting all disappointed?
What do you think?
I want to see the robot!
Do it, you jerks!
Do the...
Oh, man.
I've never been so relieved
to get punched before.
It really was embarrassing.
Why'd you bail on us, Robin?
We could have formed the
robot warrior Big Emperor.
Betrayed by one of our own.
Who would have thought?
Movie never would have left us
hanging like that, you know.
Don't ever ask me to dock
with you again. I'm serious.
All right, it's time for a fresh start!
Franky!
I hope you don't mind me
borrowing these things.
Hey, hold on!
Those are my heavy nunchucks!
All right, fine, but don't break them!
Listen, you sack of crap.
It's time to finish this.
I'm not going to let you keep
me from saving Nami any longer.
You look good!
Robin! Hmm?
I'm gonna give his left arm a pounding,
and then I need you to put
him in a submission hold!
Sure, you got it.
Mrs. Verona!
What's up?
The refrigerator's packed to the hilt.
It's almost overflowing!
There's plenty of room
left in the pantry, right?
Just use that. Yes, ma 'am.
And hurry it up with the treasure.
There had better not be one
single jewel left behind.
Yes, ma 'am!
Take this!
Let's see how you like
my special oil star!
Triple shot punishment!
Hey, eyebrows!
Give me a boost, will ya? What?
While you're carrying
those big-ass things?
Well, you're not mad enough.
What'd you say?
Of course I can handle it!
Army Tlaire!
Power shoot!
Great shot!
Slash!
Now, siens lo!
Big tree!
What the?
What's that?
I can't stand like this! I'm gonna fall!
Keep those planks coming, bro!
And hold the might of my
super mid-air stair building!
The Franky Skywalk!
It'll get us to the top, but
it won't hold much longer.
So we gotta make this snappy chopper.
What?
Super!
Top!
Doesn't matter how big you are, the
weak points of a body never change.
One crack of the jaw, and
the brain goes spinning.
You're looking a little dizzy, and
you've only got one leg holding you up.
You're going down, Luffy monster.
Cat manners!
Kick!
Court!
Your face is about to get
introduced to the ground.
Come on, fall down!
Slow start.
But score one.
This is nuts!
The mansion's crumbling.
It's almost all gone.
Why is he flipping around like that?
Is it a circus act?
I know it sounds stupid, but do you
think somebody could have taken him down?
Yeah, you're right That does sound stupid
There's no need to worry about me Nami.
I'm alright trust me There's plenty else
for you to be troubled about I guess
I'd better catch you up to speed on what's
been happening on the island Please do.
Things have only gotten worse since
your Captain Shadow was taken.
Moria placed his shadow
inside a giant super zombie,
and now it's destroying
everything in sight.
How can we get Luffy's
shadow out of that monster?
Even with the whole crew, we'd have
to come up with one heck of a plan.
But first,
there's no way I'm going back empty-handed
after all the crap I've been through.
Yes, there it is!
The treasure chamber!
Oh, this really hurts!
Stupid bunch of little sea slugs!
Now you really piss me off!
I'm gonna grind you down into pirate dust!
I've paid my dues I've given Moria a
large enough chunk of my life There's
no way in hell I'm sticking around
If I'm in danger of losing all of it
Move it,
you worthless meatbags
We've got to get out
of here Before the whole
island goes down Yes,
ma 'am You heard her Get everything off
the dock And on this ship pronto All right
who the hell is this guy don't look like
no zombie what are you doing on this
ship looking down on us doing all the work
that bastard is about as big as a bear
a bear huh you're more astute
than i would have expected
Now tell me, where can I
find your master, Merde?